

Pantelis Stathatos

Contact

Address: Skurou 25, **Phone:** (+30)

Athens

6981114657

Email:

stathatos.pant@gmail.com

GitHub pages CV

https://pantelisstathatos.github.io

GitHub ()

https://github.com/PantelisStathatos

Languages

English - C2 Greek - Native

Education

- Level 5 (EU) degree: Junior
 Software Engineer
 I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ
 Athens Greece
 9/2017- 6/2019
- Greek General High school
 Degree
 9/2014 6/2017

Personal Highlights

- o Easy Learner
- Multitasking
- o Adaptive
- Great people skills
- Communicative
- Team Player
- o Problem solver

Interests and Hobbies

- Amateur guitar playerMusic addict
- Music addic
 Web design
- Web design
- o Graphic design and Arts
- Cooking
- Video games
- Movies and Books
- PC Building and Hardware

Summary

I am a **Junior Software Engineer**, Graduate* of I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ*, with an **overall three years** into my field and more than **one year** of work experience, looking to develop my skills and gain experience in both back-end and front-end **software development**. A major part of my working experience is based on Microsoft's **.NET** Framework, more specifically with **ASP.NET** Framework, and **CI/CD** practices on a JEE product, which stems from a **Continuous Integration (CI) Engineer** Internship. In the past year I have developed an interest in **Web Development** and **Web Design**, and currently I am looking into advancing my knowledge and skills in both.

Academic and **personal knowledge** includes: Java, C, C++, C#, vanilla JS, HTML, CSS and CSS frameworks, OOP practices and modern software lifecycles and maintenance.

Work Experience

.NET Junior Developer

@ Byte Computer A.B.E.E - 2/6/2020 - 4/1/2021

- Software developer at, various MVC structured, ASP.NET (Framework 4.8 and older) products, with responsibilities that would include bug fixing, code re-formatting or fixing versioning issues caused by badly formatted .aspx files. Through those products, some experience with MS SQL was gained.
- Took extended training in Microsoft's 365 Power Platform, which included development in Power Apps, combining and using Power Automate with other components and/or products, and using SharePoint's online capabilities alongside Power Apps and Power Automate.
- For each of the above, two Projects were created to demonstrate my knowledge and understanding of the given tasks I was to be assigned. Those include a leave-request app based on the company's business needs, created as a Power Apps Canvas app, and a Employee management web app on ASP.NET Framework 4.8 using MVC structure.

Continuous Integration (CI) Engineer Internship

@ UNIFY Greece - 2/1/2020 - 2/6/2020

- CI Engineer on a Scrum team, with responsibilities such as developing, monitoring, and supporting Continuous Integration (CI) pipelines, setting-up new test suites on a CI environment, and analyzing CI tests results.
- Learned and used Tools/Frameworks such Jenkins, Selenium, VMware,
 TestNG, Maven, Git, WLS and Groovy, while getting familiar with Agile Software
 Development and CI related subjects like testing methods on a big and scalable product (Product name: Circuit).

Back-end VB.NET developer - 1/9/2019 - 27/9/2019

Certifications

- o Basics of Cryptomining and cryptocurrency trading by KORELKO Educational Institute
- o GPS and Telematic Applications by KORELKO Educational Institute
- o Game Design Basics by KORELKO Educational Institute
- Safety on Web and Social Media by KORELKO Educational Institute
- o Dark/Deep Web by KORELKO Educational Institute
- Secrets of Social Media Marketing by I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ Education Festival 2019
- GDPR Regulation by I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ Education Festival 2019
- o Artificial Inteligence by I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ Education Festival 2019
- Smart grids and challenges The Spear Project by I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ Education Festival 2019
- 2nd Anuall conference orginized by Info Mobillity World